<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Student-operated Makerspace in Camarillo, CA</title>
    <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Student-operated Makerspace in Camarillo, CA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:20:51 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rcmakes.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wine Gift Boxes</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/wine-boxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 13:20:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/wine-boxes/</guid>
      <description>Choose your design (Left: &amp;ldquo;Harvest&amp;rdquo;, Right: &amp;ldquo;Vine&amp;rdquo;) and color (Left: &amp;ldquo;Rosé&amp;rdquo;, Right: &amp;ldquo;Pecan&amp;rdquo;).
Order by Dec. 15 to receive by Christmas</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#805Strong Button</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/805strong-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:20:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/805strong-button/</guid>
      <description>Choose from four local designs
Size: 1.75&amp;rdquo; diameter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#805Strong Sticker</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/805strong-sticker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Dec 2018 12:20:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/805strong-sticker/</guid>
      <description>Size: 3 in. diameter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Cornhole</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/custom-cornhole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 13:20:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/custom-cornhole/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Westwardexpansion</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/westwardexpansion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 11:26:05 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/westwardexpansion/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradise</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/paradise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Oct 2018 16:25:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/paradise/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Academy Bridge Program</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/expandedlearning/academybridgeprogram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 16:40:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/expandedlearning/academybridgeprogram/</guid>
      <description>This three-week summer program exposes incoming freshmen to woodworking, metalworking, solid modeling, 3D printing, laser cutting, and coding to help them prepare for the multitude of courses Rancho Campana High School has to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rcfresh</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/rcfresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 16:25:04 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/rcfresh/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printer</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/3d-printer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 09:00:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/3d-printer/</guid>
      <description>Safety  Don’t use this machine if you have not received training.
 Hot surfaces! The extruder nozzle is small but it gets very hot when the printer is in use (&amp;gt;220 C, 400 F). (The entire Build Plate may be up to 105C/202F depending on the File Settings. For PLA the build plate is typically set to a warm 50C/120F.)
 Pinch Points! The instrument is a moving robot with many pinch points and it will suddenly start and stop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panel Saw</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/panel-saw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 17:14:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/panel-saw/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  Always have the stock firmly attached to the frame of the panel saw to prevent movement.
 Check the stock for foreign objects such as nails or screws before cutting. If any are detected, do not run the stock.
 Never cut small pieces with the panel saw (those smaller than 29”x29”).
 Do not cut multiple pieces at a time.
 Use hearing protection as needed at your own discretion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Router Table</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/router-table/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:48:55 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/router-table/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  Use push blocks to position your hands a safe distance from the bit.
 Large-diameter bits are for use only in a router table. Using bits over 1 in. dia. in a handheld router can easily cause you to lose control of the tool.
 Always wear eye and hearing protection.
 Take light cuts. Heavy cuts invite kickback. If necessary, move the fence closer to the bit or switch to a larger guide bearing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNC Router</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/cnc-router/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:14:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/cnc-router/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  Using the Cam G-code generation software &amp;ldquo;CamBam&amp;rdquo;, design the pattern you wish to be engraved/drilled into the chosen material. IMPORTANT: DO NOT CLOSE THE CAMBAM SOFTWARE. At the time of the writing of these instructions, we are using Cambam on a trial use basis. This is subject to change.
 Save the engraving file as a g-code, or .nc file. Save it in the &amp;ldquo;cnc router files&amp;rdquo; folder, in the &amp;ldquo;engraving files&amp;rdquo; subfolder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scroll Saw</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/scroll-saw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 16:13:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/scroll-saw/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  Make sure that long hair is tied up and clear of the workspace and will not fall forward near the blade. Do not wear jewelry or loose clothes while working. Wear sturdy shoes. Always wear safety glasses while working with power tools.
 Check to ensure that you are using the correct blade for the material that you’ll be using. Reference this page when picking a blade: Scroll Saw Blades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Cutter</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/laser-cutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:33:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/laser-cutter/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  Our Laser cutter can be used to cut and engrave onto the follow materials: less then 1&amp;frasl;2 inch Wood, Leather, Rubber, plexiglass, plasitc, paper-like materials and acrylic. It can also be used to engrave onto most metals.
 Do not turn on the laser until the casing is closed.
 Avoid looking directly at the laser when in operation.
 Be cautious about fumes that are emitted after using the laser cutter especially for plastics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plasma Cutter</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/plasma-cutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 15:04:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/plasma-cutter/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  Always protect yourself from the sparks and UV radiation emitted.
 Wear dry, undamaged flame resistant clothing and gloves (as you might for welding).
 Wear shoes that cover your entire foot, high top leather boots work best.
 Button up your shirts, collars, and pockets and do not roll up the cuffs of your pants to avoid accidentally catching sparks.
 The plasma cutter may easily cut through gloves and hands, therefore do not place your hand near the cutter or in its path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sewing Machine</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/sewing-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 16:39:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/sewing-machine/</guid>
      <description>How to Use:  Thread the machine.
 Plug the machine in and turn it on.
 Raise the presser foot by raising foot treadle.
 Position the fabric in place, and then fix the fabric with the presser foot. If the fabric edge is curled, uncurl the fabric edge with the index finger of the right hand.
 Rotate the hand wheel until the needle has done 1 stich.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mill and Lathe Combo</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/mill-and-lathe-combo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 16:20:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/mill-and-lathe-combo/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines: Lathe Saftety  Always wear eye protection!
 The three-jaw chuck is very dangerous. Make sure that the workpiece is sufficiently tight.
 Be sure to remove the chuck wrench before turning the machine on or else it will be thrown.
 Do not have loose hair, clothing or jewelry near the lathe while it is on.
 Do not wear anything on your hands or wrists or they may get caught.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MIG Welder</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/mig-welder/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 11:09:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/mig-welder/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  Check the area for flammable materials and ensure that they are stored in the appropriate area or are at least 35 feet away.
 Be mindful of the fact that the fact that molten metal may spit several feet and ignite pieces of wood or paper. You may not always be aware that a fire has started when you wear a mask, so familiarize yourself with the locations of fire extinguishers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drill Press</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/drill-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 11:01:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/drill-press/</guid>
      <description>How to Use:  Set the Speed: The speed on this drill press is adjusted by moving the drive belt from one pulley to another. In general, the smaller the pulley on the chuck axis, the faster it spins. A rule of thumb, as with any cutting operation, is that slower speeds are better for drilling metal, faster speeds for wood.
 Fit the Bit: Open the chuck, slide in the bit, snug the chuck by hand around the bit’s shaft, then tighten the chuck’s three jaws with the key.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bench Grinder</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/bench-grinder/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:35:49 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/bench-grinder/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  Wear safty goggles, or face shield, and keep dangling or loose objescts away from the machine.
 Make sure that the bench grinder is properly secured to a surface.
 If it is not properly secured, then the grinder could vibrate and move while in use, or even fall to the floor.
 Check to see that the gap between the face of the grinding wheel and tool rest (aka work rest) does not exceed more an one-eighth of an inch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cabinet Saw</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/cabinet-saw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 19:13:25 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/cabinet-saw/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  This type of saw has a blade protruding from the table and is used to cut wood. This table saw is a sawstop which means that it detects anything that is mildly conductive (including skin) and will disengage the blade as a safety feature. (DO NOT TEST TO SEE WHETHER OR NOT THIS IS TRUE).
 First, examine the stock for foreign objects such as nails or staples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miter Saw</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/miter-saw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 17:14:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/miter-saw/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  First, make sure you are following Makerspace safety precautions (tie back hair, no loose clothing, and closed-toe shoes).
 Wear a full-face protective mask and do not wear gloves.
 Be sure people around you are at a safe distance from the saw.
 Keep protective guards in place at all times
 Make sure that the blade is the proper size and shape for the arbor hole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cold Saw</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/cold-saw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:55:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/cold-saw/</guid>
      <description>How to Use  To your right on the wall behind the cold saw, there is a white box with a switch, flip the switch up.
 Then on the right side of the machine, there is a green knob, flip the knob on the right to turn on the machine.
 Above the green knob, there&amp;rsquo;s a black knob that gives you the option of High to Low or Stop, turn the Black knob to the right on the slow setting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spindle Sander</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/spindle-sander/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:36:22 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/spindle-sander/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines  Keep loose clothing, long hair, and jewelry away from spindle when in operation.
 Always use safety glasses when using the spindle sander.
 Before turning the sander on, ensure that the stock is fully clear of the spindle, as well as any scraps.
 Wait until the sander has fully come up to speed before sanding the stock.
 Keep project fully on the table and do not lift up at any point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Belt and Disc Sander</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/belt-and-disc-sander/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 16:22:11 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/belt-and-disc-sander/</guid>
      <description>Safety Guidelines:  Wear safety glasses or goggles.
 Wear a dust mask for dusty operations.
 Make sure the sander is switched &amp;ldquo;OFF&amp;rdquo; before connecting the power supply.
 Disconnect power supply before changing a sanding belt, making adjustments, or emptying dust collector.
 Inspect sanding belts before using them. Replace those belts worn or frayed.
 Install sanding belts that are the same widths as the pulley drum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Band Saw</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/band-saw/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:36:50 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/equipment/band-saw/</guid>
      <description>How to Use:  Turning on the machine is very simple
 To your left there is an On and Off switch
 Simply press the On button and you will be on your way, when you are done, press the off button. It will take about 30 seconds to stop moving, and while it is slowing down do not touch anything to it to try to stop it as this may result in injury.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giant Jenga</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/giant-jenga/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 11:13:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/giant-jenga/</guid>
      <description>Contact us for custom laser-engraving.
Storage bag included.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aromarina</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/aromarina/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 10:38:32 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/store/aromarina/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printing</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforindividuals/3dprinting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforindividuals/3dprinting/</guid>
      <description> Great For: </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D Printing Package</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/3d-printing-package/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/3d-printing-package/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Craft Cups</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/craft-cups/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/craft-cups/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Cornhole</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/custom-cornhole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/custom-cornhole/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Cornhole</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforindividuals/customcornhole/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforindividuals/customcornhole/</guid>
      <description> Great For:  Weddings   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom Engraved Water Bottles</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/custom-water-bottles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/custom-water-bottles/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Laser Engraving</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforindividuals/laserengraving/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforindividuals/laserengraving/</guid>
      <description> Great For:  Water Bottles Phones Dog Tags -Clipboards  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showtime Marquee Sign</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/showtime-sign/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/showtime-sign/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TEDx Camarillo Signage</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/tedx-camarillo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforbusiness/tedx-camarillo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vinyl Cutouts</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforindividuals/vinylcutouts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2018 13:04:01 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/jobshopforindividuals/vinylcutouts/</guid>
      <description> Great For:  Weddings    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 16:43:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>About RCMakes RCMakes is a community makerspace and industrial job shop operated by students and is located within the scene shop of Rancho Campana High School.
RCMakes may be operated by students but it is managed by the serial entrepreneur and mechanical engineer, Dave Gross, who founded RCMakes as well as NewCo Foundation in 2017. Gross graduated University of California Santa Barbara with a Bachelors in Mechanical Engineering and Environmental Studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Notice</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 16:43:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>RCMAKES Privacy Policy This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their &amp;lsquo;Personally Identifiable Information&amp;rsquo; (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Return &amp; Refund Policy</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/refund/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Sep 2018 16:43:47 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/refund/</guid>
      <description>Return &amp;amp; Refund Policy Thank you for participation in RCMAKES. If you are not entirely satisfied with your purchase, we&amp;rsquo;re here to help.
Returns You have 30 days to return an item from the date you received it. To be eligible for a return, your item must be unused and in the same condition that you received it. Your item must be in the original packaging. Your item needs to have the receipt or proof of purchase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Makerspace1</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/makerspace1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 16:23:41 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/makerspace1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Preparedness</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/ems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 16:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/ems/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rcmakesbreakfast</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/rcmakesbreakfast/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018 16:29:42 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/videoproduction/rcmakesbreakfast/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Community Makerspace Grand Opening at Rancho Campana High School</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/press/grand-opening/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2017 13:46:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/press/grand-opening/</guid>
      <description>RCMAKES, a student-operated business at Rancho Campana High School, is holding the Grand Opening of the Community Makerspace from 11:00 am to 2:00 pm on Saturday May 13th. There will be food trucks, corn hole, giant tumbling blocks, the RCMAKES store, memberships, activities, guided tours, demonstrations, kid’s crafts and more. The event is at Rancho Campana High School and is open to the public.
The RCMAKES Community Makerspace is an 1,800 square-foot collaborative work space at Rancho Campana High School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RCMAKES Engineers $250,000 in Startup Funding</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/press/startup-funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Apr 2017 13:58:56 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/press/startup-funding/</guid>
      <description>RCMAKES, a student-operated business at Rancho Campana High School, is launching with $250,000 in startup funding from engineer, entrepreneur and venture capitalist Dave Gross and his wife, Dawn Gross, Braille Manager at the Alternate Text Production Center. Mr. Gross currently teaches engineering and business classes offered at Rancho Campana through a partnership with the Ventura County Office of Education and Oxnard Union High School District. Mr.Gross will volunteer as general manager of the new venture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Speak To a Crowd</title>
      <link>https://rcmakes.github.io/expandedlearning/howtospeaktoacrowd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rcmakes.github.io/expandedlearning/howtospeaktoacrowd/</guid>
      <description>This workshop introduces students to public speaking and teaches students basics in public speaking techniques. At the end of the workshop, students will have gained skills that will help them to present with confidence in public and classroom settings.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>